ezyspot.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy | EzySpot

Last updated 05.25.2018

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at EzySpot (“company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any  
questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at info at ezyspot.com.  
When you visit our website [http://www.ezyspot.com](http://www.ezyspot.com/%22 "http://www.ezyspot.com"),  
and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we describe our privacy policy. We seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites and our services.

This privacy policy applies to all information collected  
through our website (such as [ title="http://www.ezyspot.com">http://www.ezyspot.com](http://www.ezyspot.com/)),  
and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events (we refer to  
them collectively in this privacy policy as the "Sites").

Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make  
informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us. 

TABLE OF CONTENTS

1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?

4\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?

5\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?

6\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

7\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?

8\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?

9\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?

10\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?

11\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Information automatically collected

In Short: Some information – such as IP address and/or browser and device characteristics – is collected automatically when you visit our Sites.

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Site. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Sites and other technical information. This information is  
primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Sites, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes. We also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

Information collected from other sources

In Short: We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing  
partners, and other outside sources. 

2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

In Short: We process your information for the following purposes.

We use the information we collect or receive:

* To facilitate account creation and logon process with your Consent.

* To send administrative information to you. We may use your personal  
information to send you product, service and new feature information  
and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

* To enable user-to-user communications with your Consent. We may use  
your information in order to enable user-to-user communications with  
each user's consent. 

3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?

In Short: We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations.  
We only share and disclose your information in the following situations:  
* Compliance with Laws. We may disclose your information where we are  
legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law  
enforcement requirements).

* Vital Interests and Legal Rights. We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

* Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Sites, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Sites over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand  
online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

* Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

* Third-Party Advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Sites. These companies may use  
information about your visits to our Website(s) and other websites that are contained in web cookies and other tracking technologies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

* With your Consent. We may disclose your personal information for any other purpose with your consent. 

4\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?

In Short: We use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and  
store your information.

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and  
pixels) to access or store information. 

5\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?

In Short: We are not responsible for the safety of any information that  
you share with third-party providers who advertise, but are not  
affiliated with, our websites.

The Sites may contain advertisements from third parties that are not  
affiliated with us and which may link to other websites, online  
services or mobile applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and  
privacy of data you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by  
third parties is not covered by this privacy policy. We are not  
responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and  
policies of any third parties, including other websites, services or  
applications that may be linked to or from the Sites. You should review  
the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond  
to your questions. 

6\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill  
the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless otherwise required  
by law.

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is  
necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, unless a  
longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax,  
accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will  
require us keeping your personal information for longer than the period  
of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your  
personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if  
this is not possible (for example, because your personal information  
has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your  
personal information and isolate it from any further processing until  
deletion is possible.

7\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?

In Short: We aim to protect your personal information through a system  
of organizational and technical security measures.

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security  
measures designed to protect the security of any personal information  
we process. However, please also remember that we cannot guarantee that  
the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to  
protect your personal information, transmission of personal information  
to and from our Sites is at your own risk. You should only access the  
services within a secure environment. 

8\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?

In Short: We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children  
under 18 years of age.

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18  
years of age. By using the Sites, you represent that you are at least  
18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent  
to such minor dependent’s use of the Sites. If we learn that personal  
information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we  
will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly  
delete such data from our records. 

9\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?

In Short: You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time.

Account Information

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in  
your account or terminate your account, you can:

¦ Log into your account settings and update your user account.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will delete your  
account and information (bookmarks you added) from our active  
databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to  
prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations,  
enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

Cookies and similar technologies: Most Web browsers are set to accept  
cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your  
browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to  
remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or  
services of our Sites. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by  
advertisers on our Sites visit [ title="http://www.aboutads.info/choices/">http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)  
.

Opting out of email marketing: You can unsubscribe from our marketing  
email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the  
emails that we send or by contacting us using the details provided  
below. You will then be removed from the marketing email list –  
however, we will still need to send you service-related emails that are  
necessary for the administration and use of your account. To otherwise  
opt-out, you may:

¦ Access your account settings and update preferences. 

10\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?

In Short: Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted  
specific rights regarding access to your personal information.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The  
Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request  
and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about  
categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third  
parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of  
all third parties with which we shared personal information in the  
immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident  
and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in  
writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a  
registered account with the Sites, you have the right to request  
removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Sites. To  
request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact  
information provided below, and include the email address associated  
with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We  
will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Sites, but  
please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively  
removed from our systems.

11\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?

In Short: Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay  
compliant with relevant laws.

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated  
version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated  
version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make  
material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by  
prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you  
a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy  
frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

How can you review, update, or delete the data we collect from you?

Based on the laws of some countries, you may have the right to request  
access to the personal information we collect from you, change that  
information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to review,  
update, or delete your personal information, please submit a request  
form by clicking here. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
